fly.com 2018-08-21

# Cheap Flights Privacy Fly.com us

The Fly.com website is made available by Fly Holdings, LLC. 

Fly Holdings, LLC. is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read our privacy policy below to learn more. 

### What This Privacy Policy ("Policy") Covers

  * This Policy explains the privacy practices of Fly Holdings, LLC. and its family of related companies including licensees (collectively, "Fly Holdings") and applies to your use of Fly Holdings' products and services, including the websites and Mobile Applications that link to this policy (collectively, the "Services"). For more information on our Services, [click here](https://www.fly.com/).
  * This Policy covers how Fly Holdings treats the personal information we collect and receive related to your use of our Services and Mobile App.
  * When we refer to "personal information", what we mean is any information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information, precise location data, or phone number, and any other information that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This Policy does not apply to the practices of people or companies that Fly Holdings does not own, control, employ or manage, except where incorporated by reference within licensing arrangements with third parties.
  * **_Minors_** \- You must be at least 18 years old to register or subscribe for Fly Holdings' Services because Fly Holdings is available only to individuals who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law.

### Information Collection

  * Fly Holdings may collect personal information about you when you visit and use our websites or Mobile App, when you register or subscribe for and sign in to our Services, when you open our e-mail newsletters or use Fly Holdings software widgets, when you visit the websites of some Fly Holdings partners, when you participate in a member review, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes sponsored by or in connection with Fly Holdings. For more information on Promotions, [click here](https://www.fly.com/).
  * Fly Holdings may combine the information that we collect about you with information that we obtain from business partners or other sources.
  * When you subscribe to or use our Services, we may ask you to provide personal information such as your name, credit card information, mailing address (including country of residence), e-mail address, telephone number, Instant Messaging address, birth year, gender, preferred airport, occupation, and other personal interests. In addition, when you subscribe to or use our Services, we collect and store your IP address and, when using our Mobile Application, data such as device type and OS version. Note, you are not anonymous to us when you sign in to our Services. For more information on IP Addresses, [click here](https://www.fly.com/).
  * Fly Holdings may collect information about your transactions with us and our business partners through our Services.
  * By signing up for our mobile services, downloading our mobile application or providing your phone number, you consent to receiving push notifications, advertising messages and text messages from Fly Holdings relating to our products and services.
  * When using our Mobile App, if you tell Fly Holdings where you are located (e.g., by allowing your mobile device to send Fly Holdings your location), Fly Holdings may use that information to provide you with location-based information, tailored offers and advertising. If you wish to deactivate this feature, you can disable location services on your mobile device.
  * Fly Holdings may collect third party information in connection with our gift giving service. We will collect the relevant contact information of the gift recipient which may include name, address, and email address. We will use this third party information only for this service and not to market directly to the recipient unless the recipient is currently registered with Fly Holdings independently. To provide this service, we obtain address information of the gift recipient from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service, to verify the address so we can properly ship your gift order and to prevent fraud.
  * Furthermore, when you use our Services, we receive and record information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Fly Holdings cookie information, the type of software and hardware you are using and the web page(s) you visit.

### Sharing and Disclosing Information

  * Fly Holdings does not rent or sell personal information about you with third parties, however, we reserve the right to share the personal information we collect about you through our Services with third parties when we have your permission or under the circumstances described below.
  * Fly Holdings may use the data we collect about you for the following purposes: 
    * To provide you with the products or services you have requested from us or through our Services;
    * To provide personal information, when required by law, in connection with security-related or law enforcement investigations, to comply with legal requirements, orders, or proceedings, to perform credit checks, report or collect debts owed, or to protect the rights or property of Fly Holdings, our employees, our members, and our Services;
    * To investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Fly Holdings' [Terms & Conditions](https://www.fly.com/), or as otherwise required by law;
    * To customize the content and provide targeted advertising for our Services and to improve our Services;
    * To contact you with offers by Fly Holdings and/or third parties that we think may be of interest to you;
    * To conduct research and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients;
    * We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our websites and to estimate the total number of Internet users who visit our websites from certain countries or regions of the world;
    * If you are making a purchase on the Site, we often work with third parties and trusted business partners to securely collect your credit card, billing address and other verifying information. The third parties that we have partnered with are required by contract to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information they receive and/or process on our behalf. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and thus we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We assume no liability for disclosure of personal information due to, among other things, errors in transmission or unauthorized third parties;
    * If you make a hotel booking through our website or our mobile platform, we will share your personal information with the hotel and other necessary third parties to provide you with services. Please refer to the website of the hotel you are booking for its privacy policy. Additionally, we may partner with other companies to provide hotel inventory as part of our hotel booking service. A partner consists of a third party company with which we have contracted in order to provide you with our Services featured on our publications or hotel booking platform. Should we partner with a company to provide you a hotel booking, we may share your personal information with that third party partner. Please refer to the website of the partner displayed on our website for its privacy policy;
    * We may provide data to trusted partners who work on our behalf to communicate with you about offers from Fly Holdings and our marketing partners, or to provide you with our location based services. Note, these companies do not have any right to use or share the data for any other purposes;
    * We may also provide data about your mobile device to our third party analytics partners for the purposes of tracking mobile app usage information. We will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service;
    * We may transfer, share, or disclose your personal information to third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process such as a merger, acquisition, and/or a sale of all, substantially all, or part of our assets, and/or a licensing agreement with third parties. Fly Holdings will provide you with notice before your personal information becomes subject to a different privacy policy unless the privacy policy remains tied to Fly Holdings' own practices;
    * When you enter a promotion sponsored or offered in connection with Fly Holdings, we may contact you and share your personal information with third parties so that we may administer the promotion, for prize fulfillment, and as otherwise specified in the official rules for the promotion;
    * We may invite you to write a member review on your personal experience and display the information that you provide us. When submitting a review you should not provide any personally identifiable information that you do not wish to make publicly available;
    * We may contract with third parties to analyze our customer data and/or handle web chat, email, customer services and other services. The companies we employ to help us with these tasks have access to personal data to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes;
    * If you purchase certain services for others, such as hotel reservations or Local Deal gift vouchers, we will collect the personal information of the recipients of these services. You must make sure that you have the right to provide such personal information. By providing any personal information for another person, you represent that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary consents from such person to enable us to collect, use and disclose such personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If an individual whose personal information you have provided us wishes to request the removal of their personal information they can contact us via the feedback form at the end of this policy;
  * In order to provide our users a seamless experience, some pages on our websites may be hosted by unrelated third parties. The governing privacy policy will be present on those hosted pages; and
  * Our websites also include links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Fly Holdings. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

  * We use cookies and other technologies, such as web beacons, pixel tags, and clear gifs, to personalize our Services to your preferences and to provide an automatic log-in process. For more information about our use of cookies, [click here](https://www.fly.com/).
  * Fly Holdings may use web beacons to access Fly Holdings cookies in connection with our Services. 
    * A web beacon is activated as part of a web page or e-mail and allows us to count visitors to our websites and to recognize users by accessing Fly Holdings cookies which help us personalize your experience when you use our Services.
    * Fly Holdings also uses web beacons to conduct research on behalf of our partners and for auditing purposes. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with partners from this research. For more information about our use of web beacons, [click here](https://www.fly.com/).
    * We may partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner may use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Your Account Information and Preferences

  * Fly Holdings respects your right to control how your personal information is used. Fly Holdings may give you the opportunity to request communications from vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers. For more information about these opportunities, to edit your personal information, to unsubscribe from receiving Fly Holdings services you previously requested, update your account or to terminate your account, please visit your [User Profile](https://www.fly.com/). To unsubscribe from receiving Fly.com marketing emails, please [click here](https://www.fly.com/). Users can access their account by going to their profile page. If you have any issue accessing your profile page to update or delete your account, or to request deletion of information you have provided to us, please use the feedback form below. We will respond to your deletion requests within ten business days. Users may also follow unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional email.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Fly Holdings Services or your account, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
  * Information about how to opt out of receiving communications to which you are currently subscribed is included in the communications we send to you.
  * If you request termination of your Fly Holdings account, it is our practice to deactivate your account and block further e-mail deliveries to you in approximately ten business days. This delay is necessary to discourage users from engaging in fraudulent activity.
  * We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you Services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Confidentiality and Security of Your Personal Information

  * Fly Holdings takes reasonable security measures to protect your user information under our company's control against loss, misuse, or alteration. For more information on Security at Fly Holdings, [click here](https://www.fly.com/)
  * Fly Holdings reserves the right to enhance information about you with appropriate and legal data that may be obtained to serve you better and present you more relevant information, for example by using Geo-IP maps. In addition, Fly Holdings reserves the right to take proactive steps to unsubscribe users for a variety of reasons at Fly Holdings' discretion, for example if an e-mail address stops accepting e-mail.
  * Fly Holdings complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Fly Holdings has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Fly Holdings' certification, please visit <https://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

### Data Transfer and Storage

  * Please note that the information Fly Holdings collects about you may be stored on servers outside your home country - currently on servers in the United States. If you are visiting our websites from a country other than the United States or your home country, please note that the United States or other countries where we may be hosting servers may not have the same data protection laws as your country or jurisdiction. By providing your personal information to Fly Holdings, you are consenting to: (i) the use of your personal information for the uses described in this policy; and (ii) the transfer of your personal information to a country outside your home country - currently the United States.

### Social Media Widgets

  * Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Single Sign On

  * You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like these also give you the option to post information about your activities on our Service to your social media profile page to share with others within your network.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

  * Fly Holdings may update this Policy from time to time. We will post any update(s) to this Policy on our websites. All update(s) will be effective immediately on posting.
  * If we make any material changes in the way we treat personal information, we will notify you by including a notice in an e-mail sent to the primary e-mail address in your Fly Holdings account or by placing a prominent notice on our Privacy Policy web pages and our home page.

### Questions/Your Privacy Rights

  * If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, regarding disclosure of personal information to third parties should it ever occur, or about data we may hold about you, please complete a [feedback form](https://www.fly.com/).

_LAST UPDATED: 7/7/2014_
